What s the
etiquette for
watching a movie
on a plane when
there s a sex
scene
Nudge the person
next you and let
them know it s
about to happen
Put the airline
magazine over
your lap to hide
what you're doing
and try not to
moan
Squirm nervously
until it's over
Nudge the person
next to you and
say 'nice'
When in doubt
whip it out
Look around and
if anyone's
watching make eye
contact and
wiggle your
eyebrows at them
You're welcome
have fun with
their reactions
If its your movie
that you've
brought along on
a laptop or phone
I would say skip
the sex scene If
its in a movie
provided by the
airline on the
little tv let it
run That's the
airline's issue
if someone is
upset about
seeing it
Crank up the
volume and grab
some lube to
assert your
dominance over
the rest of the
passengers
If it's on the
headrest display
I'd change the
channel If it's
on my own device
I'd angle it
different or
cover it as much
as I could Just
to be respectful
to others or if
any kids were
trying to watch
It's just a sex
scene and I
really don't care
But I'm not going
to let my lax
approach to it
affect others
It's just a
common courtesy
that's not
inconveniencing
me at all No big
deal
Loudly discussing
it with your
neighbor
I watched
"Everything
Everywhere All At
Once" for the
first time while
on a flight and
once that dildo
fight scene came
in I had no idea
what to do
Boner in the barf
bag
Go "Hm" nod your
head
inquisitively and
take notes in a
notebook
I was flying on
an alaska flight
a few weeks ago
and put on The 40
Year Old Virgin I
knew it was the
edited version
because there was
no way they'd
have butt naked
porn stars
appearing on the
whole screen
Despite that they
did NOT cut the
scene out where
they lock him in
little glass room
with porn playing
on the tv screens
Oops Luckily this
was a redeye and
everybody was
asleep
I usually go
completely still
and hope that the
other passengers
can t perceive me
unless I move
Like T rexes Or I
ll put one hand
on my chin in a
this is an
integral part of
the plot and I m
forming an
intellectual
thought about the
scene kind of
move Or I ll just
try and remind
myself that I
didn t make the
movie and it s
not my fault that
suddenly Pearl
starts humping a
scarecrow for an
uncomfortable
amount of time
rewind and play
it again
I was watching
Wild Things with
Denise Richard's
aisle seat on a
long flight Had
no idea about the
lesbian scene My
laptop had a 17"
monitor which is
HUGE for a plane
Spicy scene
starts I get
nervous look to
the guy sitting
next to me who
gives me a huge
thumbs up I turn
around and 5 men
are leaning out
of their seats
gazing down the
aisle at my
monitor I let the
scene play out
since 7 of us
were watching
A lot of airlines
I've been on Just
straight up
usually edit out
or heavily censor
those scenes TBH
but if not then I
would probably
just fast forward
through it
gt "But my cousin
Walter jerked off
in public once
True story He was
on a plane to New
Mexico when all
of the sudden the
hydraulics went
The plane started
spinning around
going out of
control so he
decides it's all
over and whips it
out and starts
beating it right
there So all the
other passengers
take a cue from
him and they
start whipping it
out and beating
like mad So all
the passengers
are beating off
plummeting to
their certain
doom when all of
the sudden Snap
the hydraulics
kick back in The
plane rights
itself and it
land safely and
everyone puts
their pieces or
whatever you know
away and deboard
No one mentions
the phenomenon to
anyone else "
Mallrats
Is the sex scene
in the movie or
is it the
passengers having
sex
I wanted to watch
Schindler's List
but after doing
some research
subjecting the
passenger next to
me to nudity
doesn't seem
correct I'll
watch it on my
own time
I saw ex machina
for the first
time on an
airplane since
they had it on
their screens
Didn't expect
that much nudity
so when it
inevitably
happened i was
like "its just
robot tits this
should be fine"
Lol
If there aren t
any kids around
watch as normal
Adults can look
away if they re
offended Kids
around I skip
If it involves
nudity skip
through it